we're gonna go to the I've been teaching
it for eight years
I promised yeah okay consulates it was
sent for certain things about some
lumber who can tell me how long room
relates to the five topics and the four
schools scheduling like a comedy maad no
it's a counter pitch is full of yours
you could see Simon got a mature
approach to pyotr velikiy
lamb bream at a mini pizza technique
bttm it exact
Abyssinia version respectively shockers
can't avoid Delta Gasol am brimming
Romania boo child Nebojsa toll
collectivist a budget of in a monastery
okay so if you have time okay it's a
guesthouse
if you don't have time if you're a
farmer in today you just once a month
but it's a good I took a channel I did
your honor
[Music]
okay let's do the whole thing in a in a
way that you can use the chemists or
sorry a little bit separate the whole
Gashi course okay if they don't have
time yes - I chose to the end of the
world today a minute left over stupid
zealots no no don't leave somebody just
come no Gazzaniga dollars that would be
a great short lamrim that you could
teach people a static work I wrote kill
Amelia
would you at the beer I would say say
baby teacher start with dad not in QT
which it's in their course mention
that's in a cetera well in case the
student quit this better so we're doing
two lamb ribs wait till him volunteer
nothing you did evening bitching you're
learning how to teach the shortest I'm
room in history up which at some of her
own Kamala marry Morgan and I'm so the
three main okay that's all change is the
shortest Norman samwick rotmg thurgood's
just and then in the morning you're
doing the longer of the longest I didn't
you were doing the great lamb room at
the Villa Columbarium for one kid in
picture who wrote the commentary for
come on daddy it could be chatting
muhammediye mom good morning sir
studying his is a champion loser okay
and you know I was having lunch with
some people I remember it was my old
lady mrs. Hancock anyway he's 93 ID and
we were like 130 what's your favorite
book of all time you know somebody said
garma the winner thrust into your hands
and I think it's the greatest book ever
written I think the rest of the summer
so check means so we're going through it
what are you calling
savoring it okay savor means enjoy the
taste
at the last but not sadly at mrs. has
promised to desert yeah be shallow you
said yes
this la mer is a huge sauna sure my
daddy Anna the Navy person amore
suspicious of things when they
misspelled the name of the leader or
like seaman under the final section of
emptiness directly okay grab a chair
start to focus on yeah focus it oh it
didn't make it huge why on years del
lugar de cobre Troy Jetson have already
did it it still doesn't copy and so I I
promise desert
oh yes yeah Michelle just yet okay Matt
we're here for a while I'm so Chi I'm
gonna be well it's just a status this is
worth coming all right so that's our
plan it's a flash blood not she's gonna
take it in the middle some reason your
Picazo oh yeah
text text back
I'm putting the text up just for you to
follow
yeah breast but text because I watch the
movie are you gonna miss my dress
Hiroshi say middle of us that's what she
ever had it's a bit spirit what you do
right yeah Jory there what them what
them you guys come on I'm sorry but you
cannot see so good let's Tiffany was so
I used to put seeds in your mind the per
student star stood beside you say my
wife says I'm gonna go word for word
yeah but do very much that says if you
don't want to study that Sookie murky
our process as I said if master says
nine you you'll be on
all right here we go down there Karen
he's quoting them down what's number Oh
dorita Wichita yeah clear thinking which
number three okay
the mother book of all clear thinking
which is by zero it chunka get to the
other kitty okay
Dharma kitty okay and it says sip a
synonym gal relation penny my intention
chipper sit your oh yes now we're
Lafleur associated with them are karma
which one
xenia karma karma Kia two and ten is
give up people chance man ah okay what's
the difference between two and ten okay
Santa Harmar deviate you're committing
Karma
okay beautiful shadow is wanaka cockatoo
somebody's making pots okay which means
um exceeds the parts are karmic seeds
okay
so then it cooks and cooks tinker don't
get loaded divisive adore is a song but
that there's not and then it's a dime
number pregnant lady reached I don't
know
so target please could be okay it's very
clear in my mind it's hard to explain
when you put the seed in the ground
beside our sleep there's a whole staff
factory staff sitting inside then you
put water on the steam which is actually
but don't believe ice water cytosine and
vice versa PI and I see this like yeah
it's a visual Kirk
it's like October in the jewelry yeah
christmas is coming
sixty percent of diamonds are sold in
one week to see all the workers are like
yeah we gotta get these water than I
serve it up with share your recipes
about to loud enough something wrong
yeah they all go crazy
military miss offense august the sea
decided to
let open the Sita's pregnancy the baby
is about to come okay
this lamb ribs right here they're
suddenly talking about what makes to go
to pen store okay Fred tree seed for
water water what is it in your mind says
nine that makes the seed go for a short
same coffee meditation good see the
heroic similar here see man
now listen okay this is deep you plant
good seeds in your and you want them to
grow then do do lots of rejoicing
participate in Africa okay got it
head up with new coffee what wakes up
the factory that's it word say it nice
very interesting and what's the opposite
of coffee manatee stop with your paw
logistically yes yeah listen a way to
get a bad seat pregnant gosh double plus
ml Raziel Oh is to not understand it I
think yep when you might give oh cool
it's very interesting that's okay the
way to make bad seeds it's just an honor
to spend how they work at the frosting
yep pretty much
okay and cool okay you would think
rejoicing the apps that would be anger
it's not is there any misunderstood
yeah
okay okay if I really understood half of
it
yeah okay so here we go he's talking
about so he says you are to stop this
dagger speed right
nicely don't do the four powers that's
very Sheila stop- sees I do they destroy
negative seeds it's not me obesity them
in the freezer throw stomachs a mirage
and then they put a lock on it you can't
destroy a negative see colliding like
that why make a new video
but you there's a justice to the
universe but there must a yes but it
goes first PC and must get hurt yeah you
can't imagine just say oh no you can't
do that wishing it it's like gravity
okay see please say light
so how Dharma Quixote says how do you
stop how do you get the guys in there
you go back to see doc with the demonic
you halation I win you my a nation pen
expand means the Karma will not be able
to throw any results okay you can shut
down the okay understand the crew is a
very cool place you see man okay
give ight you know don't nod could you
fall asleep
what do you go
[Music]
yeah you see up and you March there's
does it destroy the seed you mean yes
what no it no it still gets planted but
especially if you're thinking I wouldn't
do it it's called the morning-after pill
it's a figurative over a tablet as
opposed okay after you do something
wrong it pretty much kills the power
that's the guts of the four parts okay
Kenji Chiapas zero very beautiful
Sanchi chicken for $50 words like sides
eat chicken chicken
Thank You chicken can I'll give you a
clue for $25 numbers Cusco yeah nice as
opposed to near leg EQ okay
material cause of the tree is the seed
20 chicken is the conditions like the
water and the fertilizer okay 25 for him
shopping
she's my bank card this week okay she's
got all the money honey
alright plenty cheaper Satan or Satan or
means you killed the conditions not to
see okay he's talking about it how do
you kill look don't go after the Senate
don't go out to go after the water go
after the sunlight block you that I
disturb it's a mess but I have weeds in
my garden you know you have a choice you
can sit there and try to pull them out
all day
it's terrible work my god to do it why
don't you get the kinds of it say yes or
you could just put a piece of plywood
over there
I'll even watch the process to detain
you they don't get son change the
students to buy it you didn't take out
the plan you cut the plenty chicken
you cut the supporting condition do it
that way okay but just quit for the
negative CT go after the support it's
easier than trying to fight with the
seat okay the promotion
Stephanie you know young jr. if you
don't do that yes that it was so sure
CIPA season ago the factory it's gonna
open
don't what about it safer is technically
the name for the 8th limb make all the
initial desire number 9
what's it limbo Koopa limbo advanced
with her okay so a called
technically in The Wheel of Life
teaching it is called voice beginning
desire mature nine is called advanced
desire and eight or nine are the
sunlight question frames Daniel if
approached leave us okay
question for you I'm in the third
turning of the wheel in particular sir
are you serious is this really what you
think I should stop wanting things and
my desire this is really number eight
nine eleven is it really the answer is
no it's not desires not the problem
it's not understanding okay why in the
teaching on the traveling sunlight
called this beginning desire and
advanced it why they call it desire but
yes
Alania that's part of the answer
the Chester three at what wheel is that
teaching on the wheel
Calais or the list the list period the
wheel teaching is very why am I talking
about that I spent two hours trying to
talk about the different ideas of the
different schools okay dope would she
like to scroll are they correct no yet
only one good why the bullet teach
something is not correct but your mom
would double check doing a little higher
a cure okay got it
so now in this long rim talking to
farmers go buddy it's the same desire
bad seeds to open that sunlight okay
it's an introduction to the topic of the
question you should wait and I offer
money bring up clay sure if you want to
talk about talk about how you can kill
your bad seeds the factory so which is
this paddy the water of your mind this
morning okay got it
that is a chain yet of washed or how did
we get there
shut up gramma Christine is it is it
which is really cool if you study and
it's your school okay Stephanie you're
not lying to me - no and if you have the
Sunday service here so meaning if you
don't understand the things not only
will it open this seat but it will
attend you posted a scroll the same it
its staff will plant know someone at
specific passages okay it's a nasty it's
almost like a self-perpetuating wheel
okay it opens talk to your wife okay
right parson he doesn't have this
problem okay okay now quarterback AJ kit
saw any no money you know therefore the
very root
according me right the very root that
pins this wheel Glacius Nisha that and
nothing else me means that something
else okay so we got a talking
we got a study bring up receiver spoke
when this has nice evening okay got it
here we go yeah he said just now
Gramercy chest the whole trigger he gets
the wheel of missionaries Glacius try to
talk about it remember I didn't forget
your question Steven I'm still thinking
about it now hundred dollars
Stud dollar if I'm gonna run out of
money really is gonna ding give serious
what do someone who knows - Bettany a
few people here tell me what this next
paragraph is for $100
I just want one word I just like God not
slower so easy it's like 10 it's $10 a
letter
time's up
so ever did was slow let's read it
together
I didn't miss this much time saying
you're more shepper Shepherd wrong
num-num Kim I talked to Gemma doctor
wrong top key ranking de Casas same you
mushy seen my total war ship a Chilean
no monkeys any definition equation I
gave this morning's cheapest hundred
dollars you're a good guy time with the
service or the definition of definition
of negative thought okay here you got is
this money okay
Rangi dang it Kentucky's thinking my
shirt chip is 17 December no monkey
teeny very famous okay he made it a
little Omri me easier okay ready no Mon
shepper this thing we call clay sure
youngnam came a talk to this number the
way word this means a win it's very
unusual but just after you get one just
after it enters your mind this random
came at our to just after it top key
yeah by its own power
thank you dandy contact the person who
has it in their mind
thank you they're mine yeah Ashanti a
shunt no Shanti okay they're mine
yesterday was it the wind like you were
having a good day and the right the
bouquet is very crucial in Vallecito a
vaishnava content Taiwan one month ago
sir
Stanley divine yeah yeah it's the
fertilizer for anger you're mine now
you like it says 98 yeah we're having a
good day and then I mentioned your
boyfriend your that's the foreclosure
cases reports for us get off balance
okay so really that was balancing our
duties about and then the closure
can't come it is status there's no that
we see the balances the mine okay got it
here we go yeah my fishing he adds
something here MA - MA - yeah the mind
starts acting crazy like a crazy horse
says manumission anticipation is good no
vinaya no benaiah
here's the word okay it means swollen
amia you start at about five minutes old
boyfriend don't make a horsey vomit is
mixing my function of a pleasure to
function that's someone you
rosie was found at this number to divide
must start acting crazy start away
Mattoon like a wild horse when you're
gonna have all kinds of problems
okay that's probably Emma if we followed
our maturity on this castle yeah it's
gonna feed your negative seed
yeah the toaster budget calculus
definition yes now don't go after the
seat to do what we need your fertilizer
put over the weeds the Masonic so this
whole week we're gonna study about
Starbuck clay house populations in
starve your scene mighty God all of the
wash a question okay cool it's not just
that you become a happier that you're
all your bad sister choke yeah they are
they're saying this by the way this
glacier is sim my car tonight and the
city's potential not met themself so
that's a tricky learning this here is a
accede say me when I ask you is a seed
mental them in telling them to pull not
fit mm-hmm yeah good it lives in the
mind but it doesn't think it's not aware
as a potential enemy and says man you
know she votive says 19 technically
changing thing
the government it's a thing but it's not
mind itself it's not aware don't wait if
something is mind yes they're sort of
like sucking objects it must be aware of
objects guys waiting no that's the
answer to question but it's a cool
question all right at this point we go
to your meditation book okay you have a
special meditation book am i right
what dammit I knew you've got okay okay
this is a little book of your
meditations for a church home what's the
picture
Katinka it should be some water
navigator
okay yeah not glassy water and we did
that meditation this morning so in the
afternoon after yoga after lunch mostly
sleep I said that Moya will eat two
spots after your nap
boss listener you might want to do this
okay and even people in retreats Beth
nobody told me so I'm reading a book
about getting married life to be
different after you get married than
before you get married there's nothing
special about why did I say that
just cuz you're in between doesn't mean
okay in fact in retreat it's not gonna
change your your daily habits okay so
going what facts to have retreated your
image can
but it will quest must be to go to your
meditation okay if you're in the teacher
training good luck okay okay and that
Adam what we call it through idea images
this is one it's easier to remember
where the brush is upon it it's like
Chinese characters they are easier to
remember because they ask you in ancient
times did the turtle characters turtle
shell characters they looked a little
bit like the thing they're supposed to
represent okay so these more powerful
good okay all right
which is why Chinese are so smart okay
next paragraph say this better day
on Merson cooking the mice in Adana my
Simba Muhsin
word for I don't know 30 dollars
damn $30 more don't make you stop
talking after all dan listen what do you
have to listen yeah you gotta be able to
recognize when the waters getting choppy
vámanos the pie my idea huh okay slow
what
huh my waters getting choppy right now
okay you don't know what it looks like
again tomorrow telomeres after you gotta
know everything feels like a diamond
yeah that's when a good thesis
yes the very uncomfortable nineteen
Oscar you know comfort down I still have
it is very Sampson dream harm is not
down
you see me yeah you got a selected
it's a birthday death of a click damn it
George key question ok study your own
meditation get to recognize if it
doesn't it was like 98 bit of the good
way to do that nowadays in your life do
you get used to thinking about someone
don't wait second recognize what it
feels like
Vova said is it huh - oh not quiet
how do you feel when you start thinking
about someone you don't got questions
chat would do it kappa i don't yeah i
would say that also what do you think
penny in Komodo
in Komodo yeah you start feeling like
she says you know and that's just before
you say something just before you watch
my face smell this is a little mime
that's what it is you gotta learn to
recognize the vibrate but the muscle
itself you know and you gotta be super
sensitive to that okay but she knows
what he's doing - this okay that's got
to be a burden it's nice okay yes Lloyd
a Buddhist can be reduced
much the bridge elite warning fine with
that Sangha I'm gonna graduate she's not
yet I don't feel that guy can't believe
what he said a vehicle for very strong
it's not that
okay you gotta be able to know if you're
in a room it's glass everywhere or take
your pants off you know
otherwise you're like our target okay
you gotta get in touch with your own
smoke inhalation but it's when you start
to get upset okay you get off balance
you're not upset you're just like like
someone says you're what you know that
would like just before you
they do sorry uncle my that's where
we're gonna shoot don't wait till he's
too big to kill forget it get away from
the person we're gonna study lower
methods of removing classes one of them
is you she met avoid escalation
you know arrange your lives you never
meet them but if you don't know what
they look like chance to shoot an arrow
you have to know what the target looks
like okay got it
okay come on tampon your mimosa on my
knee so I'm gonna teach you how to
recognize that you're getting ecclesia
okay
I'm gonna actually gonna introduce us on
to the whole study we're gonna study you
already why there's two classes yes this
is a study of 26
clashers six major second depression and
twenty classes that you have negative
emotions and the second let's say if
that each name that two of our
translators translated by revealing one
from the mind only he is
so word translated it in his mind only
translated Stanley Stanley if his
permission to use his translation he
said yes tomorrow the next day no
negativity okay can you send Tim yours
uses more of a chart so send him the
chart okay and you can add that to
where's Tim you can add it to Stanley's
thing okay okay cool because but that
must have bunker in between Johnson give
you the 20 yeah the your valdemar's
but sure all his thousand-page book will
be come to 30,000 people that should be
what they had to cut it he was not
gaseous he was teaching farmers oh yes
we're gonna my link you go through his
six main clashes with him
[Music]
of our translations I take it is that we
have one translator on each great school
come on the bitty boy comes to the
school working on a team but from every
difference of cool okay cool cool Maya
okay here we go
so thank the translators and the next
picture is Leticia katinka in your
meditation book is really learning at
the at least the sixth learn their name
sheets learn what they look like so you
can shoot them
gets to know the crap in your own mind
okay how about you're familiar with
and probably three of them are running
around you don't really notice it do
this one first
- oh no such a ladies Dylan learn to
recognize was not virus yes you've been
living with them million lifetimes your
friends did yeah them each other okay
right okay so when you do that it will
do meditation number two after we
learned the six okay go on
chased excuse me but will go on a crap
trip yeah there there you haven't met
some of them listen okay okay here we go
Sonya and onion you know it's onion
onion you know back to the text
sonyeondan Union said Sun Yin Yin Yin
Yin Tong Yin Yin Yin onion tell me onion
chopped sour your mom yeah rude courting
clashes okay six the big six the Union
the Union means the 226 main ones that
we have many times every day twenty
tombola and he cheats us by the way you
know this now I'm gonna make two
presentations here yes number one six
chest main globnar negative emotions yes
secondly I'll give you the 22nd sorry
but if you study this text you can check
the Chinese translation yes he left out
the 2009 yes cuz I will be delighted
West he promises them here Bichette
first second and then he never does the
so we're taking it from Stanley alright
sir tazer name he's calling which in
Sanskrit is kosher the treasure house
which means sakharova shall be done
first one I taught you yesterday
information which is why Stanley won't
finish until 2042
yeah I will be 96 like that Oh money
baby huh
okay alright okay here's the verse from
the from the abhidharma I think it's the
fifth chapter six hours to teach our
patient ordinary America our Don Tet
semion day here's the presentation from
the abhidharma
on the six main it's our these are the
root of C peak or low bhava chakra the
Wheel of Life true and there's six of
them then he says charges this is an
abdominal wound for no more this is a
special abhidharma word for clay sure
fifty dollars to pieces of this word
it's an ACOG even give you a clue just
slow down don't answer the question till
I ask we're talking about an alternate
name for what
it's up in the middle with Vladimir at
the chest so we have we specialize our
translators some specializing in
abhidharma that's family
some people specializing in okay Tommy's
chars
saddle gay means everywhere the word
what's it mean Chad you got them all
they're everywhere in your mind your
mind is in fact encounter has deciced
it spread often your mind game and its
charm it's hard to detect them you have
cancer you don't know this is the nature
already infected there are subtle
they're hardly poison that you don't
keep you can have a coffee store do much
to viciously with Saladin mmm Melania is
just the rudest and sorry the root of
suffering chaste subtle subtle
everywhere okay don't keep it there here
they are here's the list okay norm you
know them already
desire Jalan yeah number one okay at all
anger
number two yes not yeah give me the
pieces of it anybody except Naaman
Miguel what gaupa I'm a king
yeah Karen we had a great boxer in my
generation and he would always say I'm
the great was the word slow ride yeah in
Buddhism it is yes I'm I look shape not
yeah I'm the king okay that's number
three number four misunderstanding
give that manner I mean your private
opinion -
ileum near panamanian I don't know if
you got yeah he did
50 there but then about Phil gets a
hundred because he didn't say ignorance
ignorance means not knowing miss
probably a miss knowing I think it's not
not being bad when you - nice driving
when you must not that you didn't see
your friend big difference right but I
did anybody see okay miss understanding
okay forget that
okay doctor number five Number bed
yeah how you see the world Kaka visit to
see the world world view
I mean see the room okay and there's
that's one of the main it takes now yeah
good
why you make two different but Yvonne do
why you say number four is that you want
you thought that thing misunderstanding
and then you say number five that's how
you view the world because isn't this
the same thing okay the question came up
in your mind you are nervously my
program says nanny as a choker strings
Pizza number 6 number chased kettle dark
something and we and when you teach your
students
oh but this concept of sick dad doesn't
think about it a certain kind of done
god bless ya should wait to offer money
okay yeah pleasure to question the
teacher divisive approach to teaching
it's not you change pleasure and the
question is and to question that's
healthy healthy guess that and then you
say number six chased but it's not yeah
why it's not a cliche I think it's
healthy it doesn't that old way yes
didn't ask
yes which in you expression with repeat
number four number five it means they're
still awake which in your garden if they
don't have birth
it means there's name yet on some
so we're gonna study healthy which
implies okay okay got it about why this
misunderstandings parts working on it so
the subject of doubt study doubt
cool yeah what's and what's up yeah yeah
what's the one here that done it's some
kind of doubt that's hurting you
push the Messiah dominated what it is by
the way I'll just tell you in advance in
case we all die this F yes time I said
Romeo Miya Saika so just being a donkey
the bit a slow how do you say para ski
donkey
doo-doo-doo new you you okay it's being
a donkey it means that teacher told you
clearly it was correct everything was
fine
I don't know what of us with that that
with nine years yeah I understand I
don't know if it's go work bad dog okay
got it bad dad is lazy its we're gonna
go for one more minute I'm gonna give
you a break it's a walk around and
stretch break but you do have to stretch
okay you need it this class is in the
morning are really long can you go sleep
in the afternoon I don't care don't be
the most efficient
Sonia Doug Leigh Dumbledore chutney
let's go on a trip to the subject of
desire that's gone let's explore design
that's what is she like
you need to own one northern Lewis sir
Comstock torna when you see attractive
things I see attractive things like
money like hundred dollars or loo I have
such a beautiful strong Yoga body okay
say yeah look at that you know sweet raw
come here it means beverage okay you
know look a nice cappuccino okay food
and drink etc ten thousand other things
tall enough when you see them big name
when you focus on them focus it ain't no
mindo order you don't want to tell you
never want a loser you don't my coffee
my hundred dollar question okay I don't
this is my Yoga body my you mad mind you
would say okay I want I don't want ya
shower dummies I don't want to lose it
somebody that's okay now crucial
question if you answer it I'll give you
a break if you don't wash you have to
keep going for osseous at least then
your toes doesn't bitter if you don't
answer it I'll answer it cuz I need a
break okay push the others infinitive
higher school why but you are hundred
dollars okay say it again yeah it's not
wrong to want nice yeah it's not bright
lights fish a to tell people don't have
nice cappuccinos didn't you but Ivan I
think it doesn't have health then your
coochie and I got the booties don't ever
enjoy money think I mean don't ever buy
me occupied cities at the higher school
or Laura syllogism okay really low
school you think those Buddha's in those
Buddha paradise come on they got this
big smile on their face you know this
mother eating they would I know this is
fruit the mirrors
represents all beautiful things you
could ever see
desire it is a wheel of life painting
yes that's granted desires if wanting
things is wrong okay so how's those
answers this word but his the answers
are better
okay lower school what do you have to
add to make it higher school the buy
vegetables every set of boosters yeah in
the wrong way
is it wrong to want I mean everyone okay
or do you want a world without any
beautiful things that's nothing equally
you seen I mean do you want everyone and
they're all running on 100% solar okay
okay got it
so be careful in a sea is ignorant
desire describe an English desire with a
cappuccino need to me at the premium the
cappuccino you had the last yeah what
you would take the last one in drink all
of it that's why you see a hot sugar
beets bus what intelligent is Alyssa so
the coil yeah good if I had my money I
would give you I promise okay
sharing jelly Itza is intelligent
designer usually tell
there's nothing wrong with intelligence
- yeah damn you are I like suffering so
much I'm gonna make sure we have green
drink we're gonna take a break take a
10-minute break come back by 10 20 how's
that they said about in 20 please okay
and go stretch okay we're gonna start be
fun
bleach just bitumen your solution
because you're tired I'm sorry
be tough okay I'll be tough which is
that give me throw me we're going on the
jam on this Lum room tomorrow if I have
time - new review with observing that
was the motion of a tears that we did so
soon apostate me immediately
we're doing a about a half hour every
day and we didn't oppose a so if there
were a chance to get some of the past
eight years transfer a little soup at
our Yong Hwa Yong okay
so I I have a old lady that I take care
of Mia is the visualization Ekaterina
butches I take her I don't want a man
Roger wolf keno at the bow of past ages
commercial service cliche then we went
for dinner cabinet building now
whooshing you and let's say she had
spaghetti and expects Tanya
my heart's to spaghetti at night
Michelle II write sauce and she always
wears white clothes I don't know when
you get to be 93 you don't know she
pretty much totally yeah yo yo yo
there's a difference between spaghetti
and spaghetti be aware I did you just
take it off no T plus to us yesterday I
showed the bar know if the spaghetti
sauce yes the sauce but not where you do
is stop me know if they used a lot of
olive oil
I am no God if koremasa it starts this
brand so by the time we got home no
motion other kinds of pleasures soup at
our yeah some dust on your pants good
yes yeah your socks tissue like the
spaghetti noodle let's begin
without the sauce this sauce for the
spaghetti is so you understand you want
abetting here floors nice Lola
young la easy to cannot cover easy to
get off lucubra Java de Charney by
change no July entire jelenia you'll are
changing choppa it once it's attached to
a lot simply onion like the spaghetti
sauce
it has to spread I know I'm attendances
post Rania's habit Prix which cannot
sharing needle it's Penn State's any
confidence in nature sheer desire it's
different from other classes at young
Cour very difficult to get out of the
human mind which is Turner that is yet
that is a big subject Viceroy in words
my goodness extremely well in mind only
they see microphone $0 that noise door
he's gonna explain explain yeah Abby's
knee okay there are cinemas game Scala
or Tim I don't care
my link will external heat some some
package
yeah but the Midland letter and lyrical
community-driven okay now that mr.
Bhuvan
pristine heme modular as Nicola Buddhism
a personal nature
the verbal chakras Delaney and hinayana
Mahayana to his Mahayana some sample
whereas Matra viscosity some sample is
Ned Tolkien call a Tolkien at the school
of Buddhism
Kotori three version which axman's is
the solution e mo me NT of scholar a
Turkish as nanny and then a business
jets on copy you come in tied in your
offer
Slava Tom acaba de Atacama it has
matured floors now Troodon ax column
I'll stir co-edited voice him South Nani
the usual fists as many Kadets Kadets
Kadets of mr. castaigne ma who is up a
book from Albert the chest chest which
means listener kita in disability
Naftali Turkish Nonya his the bubbly
knee should bow exercise Nicole she
scurries in Yui noon at the Teresa most
annual New Moon's Nasheed cliche
catarah wishes but Marissa retreat
actually Tolkien least the the ponies
Nexus Nonya mystic tyranids
says my her needs Ximena Condit at as
Nova the Cochrane Alicia Grenada Samina
negation coverage and hygienic they said
how idyllic the hernia Ximena Nui at mr.
Jia Jia problem irishman tell me problem
we live ecclesia her NASA colonies see
it's a cat with Morrissey passes that
should national was not normal basic
fish stew at leachate escalator call a
drug douche code was not normal bottom
three messages my
absurd name kini go chest Kaka commodity
died stitch near one of co little cone
Stas machete bullsh in yet mint Alhambra
Cheney near to Berkeley Asia
yes Lee was he so delicious - MA
Couture Couture is the Utica problem
let's learn it's not neat a key moment
of a tech ninja the most aggressive
attack of polyp which is kids cassette
Nabokov I'll name the periodic the
Sanjeevani Sorna Pingree provodnikov at
a treaty topic / follow minded little
call it a slip wound cattorini riveted
on even yet keep reasoning but
humanist it has opportunity at religious
scholar
but school at welcome to Annapolis
deprival net yet
Lord Buddha was casa o Stata poster
Stoughton eBoost I started priesthood it
is washable mashed yeast omnis immundus
this technique is key that oneness Lorna
if consequence of this yeast acid versus
non negative emotion my business yeast
starter stone with real color medium
study hernia 30 Samina cactus teach near
1aqaq is both that mental homogeneity of
show which in 2000 a set him at Radley
church called mind only at a play
envelope Allah has provided one mission
yes leash yes Russia no meeting unique
um she does cruciate Ranieri she twists
east as nanny ooh ma says nanny a glass
as many mush lenience as nanny Roche
cocked up with the stick desta gate in
nirvani akhada Basu birthday et cetera
Cheney it is measures to be published to
Roche Israel says ninety but instead TV
she chased him
Ely was repressed the static about the
chest is he probably a modest äôt with a
skew it you need epochal visit his
vulgar caucus is this poor Otto static
we are hard finish Cole le Bodhisattvas
move over omnia wishful even is stop
risk aversion movement actor marginally
Prost Prost of the Roche is Kokubo Tamia
cactus Rosetti
most covetous q88 oldest us 9ye liver
problem Hammad circulation when you
reach nirvana
stop recruits one color to distinguish
near running over bid army near honest
at chameleon wanna be the start of a
bidder me when you purchase you don't
appear foolish to resolution clarity
she's a mere one over school abhidharma
the surgeon cuts out the tumor they cut
out the brain knows the delay supportive
delay she was mr. destiny genius diodes
at videos posted on a premium nirvana
business tadka table shyness passive
initial vdd crummy pasta tino khodataeva
who leashes at warp at the tag database
estates of data static noise whatever
specialist am Regina of share shot
camera Cheney chase you she is very
interesting you have a seventh
my stab with you Oh your aunt says
Mannion delicious at the clear the bag
of clothes in this bike yet clear she
Russian in number eight if I smaller is
the refrigerator at the height where you
keep all your Samina why does mind on
this question
Manish colleague worried that when your
husband yells Christian today he's not
outside the stoniest Naru but emotional
at which a it
okay open good okay last mrs. Manion
this week the seat open epitopes just
marry me Juliet cravat sigiriya in the
reference of holiday okay high school
says the solution Chicago over at C -
Krishna remind on the squash blossom
slopes no moonlight the thing that you
cited about your text some of us in
extreme 67
he is misunderstanding and maybe that I
will never any money over Sigma is
magnificent Jamie it's just
understanding it develop when you're
getting near Paris more only polisher at
any privately have you misunderstand
where your goods yet the widgets at the
refrigerator don't so I didn't make you
know something that's the whole process
of liberation and sansara
in the mind on this core Virginia school
seven is looking at husband is out in
the kitchen you won't achieve Manasa
this is my initial version on the
furniture
and it's cool sure you have a bag of
what is called Russia Union you need and
then you're gonna
coochy coochy foundation continuity by
hearing yourself I see back recharge you
me put we imprinted keep so I am Amir so
in the mind only son keeping you out of
Nirvana II and which causes you to have
anger is that number seven doesn't
understand number a preaching at the
worst we near the stealing your honor
sorry
looks clear shots Madrid Muhammad unique
in yep I own opinion might now the
original sure is practice practice
viscosity term right Chum lactic yeah
but how do you destroy seven chakras
rachet tea seed more yeah you just see
what the hell's going on in the if I
press the smoothie to rock quarry cigars
that I didn't my husband didn't come
from welcome ten minutes before we show
is invited to yellow
you understand brain dolkha touched only
prayer upon you my voice and what for
$300
he's a tree stood over a I was
gonna say a thousand but I'm losing yes
this Jeannette emotional I know you're
interested
that'd be convenient to forget the
question and yes
yeah I remember the question yeah españa
what's going on
stop please hold it when numbers what's
the what's the root or the siege chum
salmon not understanding the husband
daughter you see me brighten up in your
mind you know she's your semen what's
awesome
what's a question someone's gonna ask
you gross yes that's why it's 300 bucks
on this cool little co-angler lives in
number 7 avoid more business in number 7
okay there's three its focus let me see
the moisture field opening in number
eight
move could hit Nicosia the easy question
it's not to turn in a dollar question
easy question Estella present her
husband yelling in the kitchen move
could shift meconium know yet he's
yelling inside in the more rich hitman
three number of ocean okay now my
question to yeah why does seven think
number eight is outside which he move at
the same sorry inside but Shamu at the
same and of no tree but a musta but no
mercy at the hydro Qaddafi who did
mental named Virginia at a Dominion at
the Machine turn on their voice him on
some senior in facility yet okay be
aware
I just want to make that clear first
across the heck of a subdivision of many
motors and I'll make the easier question
unease associated tasted or a problem
why but you more according to the mind
on this a glass school a little real
like at the trust inside is other stuff
nutrients why she want to just do it
vitarka says 98 a battery operated
dietetic mine you really trust all of
you in your own mind but human are some
really rich human is not ocean she
should get $300
oh that does not pollute III stood over
say it again
are you close the email of revulsion
countless lifetimes this is not a word
me outside man jerky Baskerville wolf
snarled and you keep our segment you key
key party rock chat where did I teach
you that I never taught you that it
takes as many yes that's a life cut
already she's not understood you have
talked to your friends if we go very
nice very husband Oh Tom and because of
that talking if the most that was life
if we make you wait here when he's
really just in your says many but they
are receiving visitors tomorrow Jimmy
some I can answer chicken yet the way oh
yeah nice
second the latter cool garlic it's a
very sophisticated system and it's
pretty cool it's pretty cool if you
really understand the mind on this cool
his daughter was pretty final opinion my
team why are we talking we were on this
get nuts sumo and red berries funny
isn't it young Kawa that oil stain it
has no me de Vaca extra it tends to
annoying meet them once you refused to
share a cup of coffee
which destroy your learning it's the oil
the Muslims pastrami especially what was
the second quality if that register hard
to get out hard to get out very hard to
get out you know you should see her
white hands
he's pirates etc they kind of look like
Panther pants no but she won't belittle
me like I wash them in washing washing
extreme strain strain be loosed on their
most lips mmm with black spot yeah hard
to get out and that's why but you move
yeah when you cut that tumor gamma V
design with the brace is a nice morning
human being and take out conscious in
this number seven not kill the human
being is it possible to clean the mind
more dinelli actually possible to get
spaghetti spaghetti in the pair is
muslim ability manipulative standoff is
often the mind on this course mister
venerable fill a little field mouse
by the way excuse me the mind only
school says you must I'm sorry the
abhidharma school says it's closed the
dynamic about it
you must burn the pants hey tummy
there won't be a michael afternoon honor
those are Michael cook with the
post in Iran at least what trainee
estates yeah
my chanel say it again available Phil
said a venial sin skuzzle-butt the works
o
klaris yeah no she clear she didn't yep
any money okay and we we definitely
going to talk about it bye Troy
prevention is letting media liaison put
emotional credit hmm now let me say one
more thing about consciousness
mentioning I barely remember
consciousness seven door closes I think
he puts the hore she see my other mental
functions at the issue if you say 51
mental function so if you destroy seven
on society she daughters of a pleasure
consciousness but it's not 100% clear
sure it's like 80% other thoughts at any
told Cosima the needle cochlear shut
issue a mystery and there's a cannula
yeah okay alright here's Charlie listen
JJ song the shalwar car difficult to get
rid of okay that goes to an item what it
means but it's a guitar is pirates FK
car team what's your item stream Russia
okay car team cover some texts work
well picture those a cartoon car yeah
the guy got spaghetti
I'll say it again and I wash - its
standard it's always why am I talking
about that mr. fonsella thought that you
two can agree is it I cannot tell you
some interesting it I'm just witnessed
at interior
it's from a tantric poem
at least and reaches kameena they must
never put to you about
sukhavati also paradise of Amitabh on
the right amitaba paradise it's a poem
about I mean it was paradise
yes ticket Varinia or meters of cities
in Ypres clear she okay what's it mean
she said as much the the verse says
quartz an arching great you are we
chained in the prison yeah of suffering
tiny look at that yeah desire pleasure
clear line yet okay but you are chained
we - I'm sorry
it mustn't move desire Selenia not
sharing it wouldn't it be interesting to
see the other three lines height oppose
marriage - Tom - that is my show 33 is
through freedom and we can only do that
because of the hard work of John Brady
good idea that much thought John but I
did such a lot of work are you all right
I'm okay here's the whole verse okay
database right Christina Christina
Ramachandra stands alone or five million
yeah so you're talking five million
pages okay
Amelie one of straining it's just rain
so it is a three sequence type a
cemetery here's the whole verse both
attack thirsty good Varinia
but really all Muslim uppity and why did
he think of that what was he doing when
he is a chef with him career okay
hundred signatories up to sock torching
the sword of anger it's cheap boniva
assassinates
Reaper selenium why what you want yeah
it kills your positive device that's the
first there's a charlatan and the
handcuffs of desire say carry grease
thank you into the prison of sunshine
it's the cheetah mice I'm sorry Leakey
juicy Pidgeot secure the rushing river
of your karma carries you to the ocean
got a nice shot was bully carries you
down the mountain to the ocean if it
counts threading yeah not gay and when
you get there waves only kick garnishee
yeah you get old rush was studying
constantly having back problems
bullying chronic pain I need to speak
poorly bully French tickler tsunami
tsunami of the chronic pain mysteries me
Francesca bullet carried down by karma
anger can you align your poem it was an
effect
I know is that caramel a delicious
welcomed by a brunette Catherine William
chess is a jewel chuckles oh man Academy
peplum
without flashes there's no Karma
bs cannot collect thing Amash let's go
to the mind on this code who wants to
explain that statement in the - circuses
nanak tohe chatters kvetch it's a toe
touch coziness Croatia's yes kaliesha
yet Carmen
yeah unless if you don't think your
husband yes yet then you're going you
know what it sir you won't yell battle
anyway just create any robot yet nice
got it
penny Abner in the mind on this square
little kisses Mannie if mines section
seven
yes the understands of justice to my
chest up mostly Chi and the husband
didn't reach it
don't reach for it is Minya then dr.
Hartman seven can't be married apartment
tada I chased him a night anymore
satisfy with sudden when I change the
voicing the husband attacked Allen you
booted me chest won't make nuclear my
chest ocean debris that the via tater
then you both know Karim from but
everything censuses the right normal
karma uh yeah but only thirty ones hmm
I think right word am i right I think so
we didn't get there yet we'll let you
know next year okay I know him you wanna
lead the Madonna
Tim Couch mandolin let me steer the
vitamin da
[Music]
yeah buddy some gesture make the
and our cool thanks for being so patient
believe me as noted last time he has
managed the husband I believe it was
Talan you're very brave to come here but
she's merely a favorite should I use
nobody in the world except you I'd
rather you either release Elise mochila
a suddenly